http://presentek.com/privacy

X
We use cookies to help make the site work properly and to analyze how it is used per our Privacy Policy.
Click here to agree and close this banner.
Privacy Policy
By using this website, you acknowledge acceptance of this privacy policy.
We do not collect personally identifiable information.
Website usage statistics are collected using Google Analytics. You may view more about Google's data protection here.
We use cookies to help make the site work properly and to analyze how it is used per this Privacy Policy.
As a result of interactions with us using a social network, we may communicate with you using that social network or other channel appropriate to the communication.
We do not sell or rent email addresses or contact information to List Marketers or other unaffiliated companies.
This site may contain or permit links to other sites or applications. We are not responsible for the performance, content or privacy policies of 3rd party sites or applications. Users are responsible for their use of any 3rd party content, data or images including ensuring their right to use this content for their purposes.
We may update or change this privacy policy.
Partner with Presentek
Let's get started
Give us a call or send us an email, and we'll get right back to you.
Message us
Download Services Overview
Sign-up for our email newsletter with sales and marketing insights from the trenches.
© 2020 Presentek, Inc. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
How can we help you? 408.354.6051
Presentek is the creator of Flipdeck.
×
Newsletter Sign-up
Name
Email
